

# JEROENJANSEN USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

Call +62 812-4385-6320 Email jeroen.b.jansen@gmail.com Website jeroenjansen.net

> Facebook /jeroenbjansen Linked In #jeroenbjansen

# **SKILLS**

Design
Concepting
Prototyping
Research
Heuristics
Wireframing
User Testing

# **ABOUT ME**

## Why I am passionate about my work

I love UX because it always requires something different. Learning about a target audience, what works, and applying that knowledge. The repeated iterations to improve products is a never-ending cycle with always a bigger goal on the horizon. What appeals to me in this is that a perfect product or design doesn't exist, but a perfect fit for the right target audience does. Tailoring products and experiences for the right fit is something that I am passionate about.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

2018 - Present

#### Freelance work

User Experience Designer

Started working on several freelance projects from this time onwards. Still ongoing.

2021 - 2022

#### Mixbook

User Experience Designer

Beautiful photobooks and print services. Worked on the internal rework of the shopping experience.

2020 - 2021

#### C Channel Indonesia

User Experience Designer

A company specialized in social media interaction. Helped develop an onboarding experience for a new project.

2015 - 2016

#### Shakr

Motion Graphics Designer

Professional advertisements made available to small business owners. Worked on new features and designs.

2014 - 2015

## Garlic

Graphic Designer

Real estate focussed design agency. Worked on new and upcoming design projects in real estate.

# **EDUCATION**

2017 - 2022

# Communication & Mutlimedia Design

The Hague University of Applies Sciences, the Netherlands

2012 - 2016

## Graphic Design

Grafisch Lyceum Utrecht, the Netherlands.

## REFERENCE

Product Manager

## Igor Putina

+373 609 44 888 iputina@mixbook.com

# **DEFINING TRAITS**

- DESIGN THINKING
- HIGHLY COMPUTER SAVVY
- EMPATHETIC
- FLEXIBLE
- INDEPENDENT, GOOD AT ORGANIZING MY OWN TIME